Paul Abelson Papers 5192
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Agreements, 1913-1936 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous clippings, reports, constitutions, notes (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous clippings, reports, constitutions, notes (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Lish Brothers vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Berkowitz & Bloomfield, Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Edelglass Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Bunkin & Seldin vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Novelty Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Aurora Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- M. Schacter vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Victoria Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Jean Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- D. Fagan & Sons Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- J. Feiner Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Chick Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Walker Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Lanrose Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Flaum & Saltzers vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Simble Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Nomark Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Cecele Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Paige Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Holly Hat Co.. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Brae-Burn Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Novelty Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Lily Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Salfelts Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Edelglass Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Bunkin & Seldin vs. Cloth, Hat, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union (CHCMW), 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- A. DelMonte vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Berkowitz and Bluemnfeld vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Quintet Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Croyden Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Walker Hat. Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Doris Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Fruhauf & Musyl vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Witty Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Sun Millinery Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- M. Schacter & Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- J. Feiner Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Gilbert Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Berkowitz & Blumfeld vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Gilbert Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Excelsior Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Quintet Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Mennen Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Lora Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Bunkin & Seldin vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Lora Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Walter K. Marks vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Quintette Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Brae-Burn Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Hermet Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Baldwin Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Lilly Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Legion Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Smith Brothers vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Eleanor Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Pilgrim Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- L&B Karo vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Salfets Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- More Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- D. Fagan & Sons vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Croyden Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Alfreda Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- M. Schachter Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Sam Mittler, Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Parfait Hats vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Hy-Dan Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Morris Schachter vs. CHCMW, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Mme, Aline Hats vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Prager Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Academy Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Cohen & Duncan vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Parfait Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Niva Hat Co. Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Ambassador Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Draper Hat Co., Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- J. Portney & Sons Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Paul Pleating & Stitching Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Penmill Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- D. Fagan & Sons, Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Parfait Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Morris Schachter & Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Lish Brothers & Brae-Burn Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- D. Fagan & Son vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- M. Levinson vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Fashion Bilt Hats vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- M. Levinson vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Selby Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- More Hats Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Abbott Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Alkay Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Mille Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Style Value Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Design Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Shulman & Waxenfeld, Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Harmon Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Joseph Richland & Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Marlin Hats Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Ambassador Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Tower Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Cameo Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Sanes Hat Co. Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Mme. Aline Hats Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Adler & Einhorn vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Cameo Hat Co., Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Sellbest Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Miramar Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- J. Finer & Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Comet Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- L&M Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Dressy Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Julius Bloom vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Consolidated Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Dee-Dee Hats vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Croyden Hats, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Olympia Hat vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Alkay Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Simble Hat Co. vs. United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International (UHCMW), 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Paul Pleating & Stitching Co. vs. UHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Great Northern Hats, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Shelbourne Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- J. Finer Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Arrette Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Beatrice Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Rosembaum Hats vs. UHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Levinson Brothers vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- More Hats, Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Cavalcade Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Simble Hat Co. Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- New Lass Hat Co. Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Finer Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Prager Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Irving Cohen vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Charles Shulman Hat Co. vs CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Priscialla Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Dorothea Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Great Northern Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Dona Hats Inc. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Julius Bloom vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Model Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Redfern Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- O'Connell Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Planet Hat Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- M.G. Kantor Co. vs. CHCMW, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Sanes Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Ben Kanrich Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- R.H.R. Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Marlin Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Parfait Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Go Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Moran Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Lish Brother's vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Academy Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Pickfair Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Lish Firms vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Lanrose Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Luxor Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Sellbest Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- M. Levinson vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Sanes Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Academy Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Jesse Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Elizabeth Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Beatrice Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Sussman Hat Corp. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Crown Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Charles Shulman Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Ambrose Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Fashion Bilt Hats vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Marcia Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Sally Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Mennen Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Prager Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Sussman Hat Co. vs. UCHMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Lesser-Brasel Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- D. Fagan & Sons vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Sun Ray Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Lincoln Hat Co, vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Beatrice Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Parfait Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Sonora Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Quintette Hat Co. vs., UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Nora Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Codette Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Syruth Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- KiKi Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Rothchild Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Brae-Burn Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- S. Mittler Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Lish Brother's vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Florette Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Kass Brother's Manufacturing vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Romico Hats vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Tower Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Sanes Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Jackland Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Lamar Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Goldsmith & Perlman vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Mennen Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- U.S. Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Bermil Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- D. Fagan & Sons vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- J. Finer Hat Co., vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Bernie Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Metro Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Jill Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Dora Fay Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Abe Del Monte & Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Sussman Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Nora Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Ambrose Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Rob Roy Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Rosenbaum Hats vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Design Hat, Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Pickfair Hat Corp. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Goldsmith & Perlman vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Simon Hat Works vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Mennen Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Imperial Novelty Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- D. Fagan & Sons vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Somax Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Bantam Hats. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- D. Fagan & Sons vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Salfair Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Cameo Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Stylise Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, Henry Bleek Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Lincoln Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Luxor Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Cohn & Patrick vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Willow Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Dene Donna Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Somax Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Markel-Taylor Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Dorothea Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Ramie Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Limelight Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Lesser-Brasel Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Salfair Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Rosenbaum Brothers vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- More Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Ander Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Joe Cohn Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- M. Schacter Hats, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Alvina Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- B. Lichtenstein vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Singreene Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Import Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Stylish Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Ardsle Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Priscilla Hats, Inc. vs UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- J. Finer Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Sherbourne Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Ander Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Caprice Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- J. Richland & Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- North Atlantic Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Rosenbaum Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- S. Caro Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- F. W. Nelkin vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Bobson Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Guy Anderson Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Harry Furst Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Redfern Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Annabel Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Fashion Prom Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Priscilla Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Sobel Brothers vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- M&M Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- B. Kanrich Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Marion Valle vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Stylish Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Benson Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Nora Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Lady Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Sussman Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Mutual Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Tower Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Ardsle Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Nara Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- M. Levinson & Brothers vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Sally Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Lincoln Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- J. Finer & Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Princess Pat Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Lesser-Brasel Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Salfair Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Lee Shaw vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Cameo Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Eisenberg Brothers vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- F&W Nelkin vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- J. Finer Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Princess Pat Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Bobsom Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Abe Del Monte & Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Farrington & Evans vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Parfait Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Pert Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Stuart Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Am Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Levy & Shulman vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Bobsom Hats, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Attractive Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Marvin Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Redfern Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Am Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Bampton Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- F&W Nelkin vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Brandt Millinery Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Bobson Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Fashion Prom Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Winchester Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Baldwin Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Rosenbaum Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Morris Schacter & Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Joe Cohn Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Brandt Millinery Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Croyden Hats, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Nat Frank vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Fashion Prom Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Brandt Millinery Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Harry Solomon & Sons vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Duane Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Gafmor Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Am Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Nat Frank vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Winchester Hats, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Ramie Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Charles Shulman vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Rosenbaum Hats vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Farrington & Evans vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Attractive Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Alert Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Gruber-Kranz Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Farragut Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Luxor Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Bernard Workman Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Attractive Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Paree Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Ben Kannich Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Marlin Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Lydia Modes vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Goldstone & Weber vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- More Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Dave Herstein vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Cameo Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Croyden Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Ellen Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Bantam Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Ardsle Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Attractive Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Redfern Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Taub and Goldberg vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Paree Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Florette Hats vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Princess Pat Hats vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Mennen Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Florette Hats vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Fashion Prom Hats vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Eisenberg Brothers vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Lee Shaw vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Joe. Cohn Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Lesser-Brasel, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Ander Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- More Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Six-Way Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Tower Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Brandt Millinery Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Kass Brothers Manufacturing vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Baldwin Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- J. Weiss vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Quintette Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Jedco Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Lucrene Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Winchester Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- J. Finer Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Donald Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Madewell Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- J. Adler Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Lily Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Parfait Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Dowager Hats, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Davidson Hats vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Jill Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- J. Richland Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- More Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Chesterfield Hats vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Quintette Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Walter K. Marks vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- M. Levinson vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Guy Anderson vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Hinchley Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Fashion Prom Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Brandt Millinery vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Biltmore Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Fashion Prom Hats vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Mario Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Park Avenue Hats, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Biltmore Hats, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Lesser-Brasel, Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Jowill Novelty Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Hollywood Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Blltmore Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Gafmor Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Sobel Brothers Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Ajax Hat Leather Co. vs. UHCMW, 1938-1939 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Ajax Hat Leather Co. vs. UHCMW, 1938-1939 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Stylepark Hats Inc. vs. UHCMW, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Beatty Page vs. UHCMW, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Ruffelt Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1915-1935 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  plus undated corres.
- Correspondence, 1915-1938 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Clippings, broadsides, publications (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Independent Theatre Owners Association, Inc. vs. Moving Picture Machine Operators Union, Local 306, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  November
- Marcus Loew Booking Agency vs. Moving Picture Machine Operators, Local 306, 1939-1940 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  Dec to Feb